我刚刚给你展示了如何用 Node.js 做多阶段的建设
So I just showed you how to do
a multistage build with a Node.js
应用程序，对吗 ?
application, right?
我现在要你做的就是我要让你做一个
So what I'm gonna have you do now is I'm
gonna have you do a multistage build with
就像一个静态的网站
like a static website.
这一个叫静态资产项目。
This one down here that's
called Static Assets Project.
这里有所有指示和
So, here's all the instructions and
如果你在这里滚动看我的答案我就觉得
then if you see right here to scroll
down to see my answer, I just feel like
如果你在这里滚动就会有很大的空间它会给你展示答案
a big space if you scroll all the way
down here it will show you the answer.
这也是我之前给你看的 GitHub 存储库
It's also in that GitHub repo
that I showed you earlier.
那么，您有多少人熟悉 Create React App?
So how many of you are familiar
with Create React App?
想象一下你们中的许多人，对，如果不是在 Fronsend Masters 中有那么大的粗粗
Imagine many of you, right, if not there's
a great coarse in Frontend Masters
这就是第 5 版 React 的完整简介
that's called the complete
intro to React version five.
好吧，你不必再做任何 " 重做 " 的部分了
All right, you don't have to do
any of the React parts of it.
我们只需要创建 React 应用来为您打掉一个项目。
We are just gonna do Create React App
to scuffle out a project for you.
所以，我们还是先开始吧。
So, let's actually just go ahead and
get started.
就像我让你和你的 React 部分一起跑
Like I'll get you up and
running with the React portion of this and
那么我将离开您构建实际 Docker 文件。
then I'll leave you to build
the actual Docker file.
这里的想法是我们要创建一个 " 创建雷act应用" 。
See, the idea here is that we're
gonna create a Create React App.
我们要把它建成一个建筑项目对吧
We're gonna build that into
a built project, right?
然后我们会把所有这些文件复制到一个 Nginx 容器
And then we're gonna copy all those
files into an Nginx container and
Nginx 容器会为我们提供所有静态资产好吗
the Nginx container is gonna serve all
of our static assets for us, Okay?
所以让我们继续吧我要复制这个可爱的小熊
So let's go ahead, I'm gonna just
copy this cuz it's really long.
Npx ，这将运行 " 创建 - 响应"应用程序。
Npx, this is gonna run create-react-app.
最近他们就像上周一样改变了创造反应应用的方式
They recently like probably last week,
changed how create-react-app works so
我必须彻底改变这个
I had to totally change this.
昨晚我做了一件好事
It's a good thing I tried this last night.
很尴尬的可爱的
[LAUGH] Cuz that would have
been real embarrassing,
React 老师对 React不了解
the React teacher doesn't
know shit about React.
我是说也许是真的谁知道呢
I mean, might be true, who knows.
好了我们要回去了你要干什么
All right, so we're gonna go back in,
what are you doing?
别这样
Stop that.
好吧那我就在我的 " 去集装箱 " 项目里了对吧
All right, so I'm here in my
intro-to-containers project, right?
我会指挥我在那里说的
I'm gonna run that command
that I said in there,
直接从晚上开始就可以了
which is gonna run it off of npm directly.
它会运行 " 创建 - 反应-应用" 。
It's gonna run create-react-app.
它将创建一个称为静态资产项目的项目。
It's gonna create a project
called static-assets-project.
这将是典型的版本，而我们并不是混淆不清的纱线。
And it's gonna be the typescript
version and we're not confused yarn.
为什么要使用 TypeScript?
Why are we gonna use TypeScript?
这是我让你使用更多微软产品的另一个伎俩。
It's another ploy for me to get you
to use more Microsoft products.
其实我只是想让你像个建筑过程一样
Actually, I just wanna show you like
as involved as a build process as
有可能，对吧 ?
possible, right?
这其实并不重要。
And that doesn't actually really matter.
因此，这需要几分钟时间来完成所有设置。
So this will take a couple
minutes to get everything set up.
如果您收到一条说明，说明您没有关联的模板
If you get a note that says, you don't
have a template associated with your
这就是我在做这件事时所看到的
project or something like that, which is
what I was seeing when I was doing this
昨天晚上，卸载您的全局安装 " 创建 - 响应"应用程序。
last night, uninstall your global
installation of create-react-app.
这就是我最终解决的问题。
That's what eventually solved it for me.
此忽略现有，希望该忽略
This ignore existing,
hopefully should sidestep that for
你，但是如果没有，这就是我最终解决问题的方式。
you, But if it doesn't, that's how
I was eventually solved problem.
好吧这可能需要花 30 秒的时间
Okay, this will take maybe, I'm gonna
guess like 30 more seconds to get through.
因此，这将安装使用 TypeScript的 React 项目。
So, this is gonna go install a React
project that uses TypeScript.
然后就为了好玩你和
And then just for fun, you and
我要把 SAS 放到 SAS 里，就像一堆依赖性。
I are gonna go put in SAS as well just
to have like a bunch of dependencies.
你会在这里看到我的笔记，我把它写在上面，它是可有可无的。
So you'll see here my notes,
I have this where it says optional.
我要这样做但如果你不觉得有什么感觉
I'm gonna do this but you could totally
skip this if you're not feeling it or
给你点东西
something breaks for you.
但我把它放进去的原因是如果你运行节点模块
But the reason why I'm putting this in
there is if you run the node modules and
npm 安装在本地，这将在您将其复制到容器中时中断。
the npm install locally, this will break
when you copy it in the container.
它将为 Mac 或 Windows 构建它，并且不会为 Linux 构建它，
Cuz it'll build it for Mac or for
Windows and it won't build it for Linux,
除非你在 Linux 上我不知道怎么打破电脑
unless you're on Linux then I don't
know how to break a computer.
我可以试试
I could try.
发生什么事了
What is going on here?
你真是太好了
Well, that's nice of you.
好了好了好了好了
All right, there we go, happy hacking.
所以现在如果我们进入静态资产项目
So now if we go into
the static-assets-project, You'll
这里有个比较完整的项目
see here you have a relatively
full project here.
我想让你做的第一件事就是让你创建一个 dockerignore。
The first thing I want you to do is
I want you to create a dockerignore.
让我们打开并编辑该文档库忽略缺省情况下不会出现的文件库。
And let's open and edit that dockerignore
file cuz that won't come by default.
就在这里
Inside of here, So
你也可以进来说新文件， dockerignore，对吗 ?
you can also just come in here and
say New File, dockerignore, right?
我们将忽略 .git 目录
We're gonna ignore .git directories and
我们会忽略 node_module 目录我们也会忽略
we're gonna ignore node_module
directories and we'll also ignore,
好吧那就好
Yeah, anyway, that's fine.
这里也可能有个缓存
There might be a cache in here as well.
不我不觉得有
No, I don't think there is.
总之我们会先做的好吗
Anyway, So we'll do that first, okay?
我想让你到这里来的另一件事是我想让你说 npm 的安装。
The next thing I want you to go in
here is I want you to say npm install.
这是可选部件，节点 - sass。
This is the optional part, node-sass.
然后我们就会到这里来
And then while that's doing that,
we're gonna come in here and
我们要重命名源文件
we're going to rename our source file.
这是 App.css，只需右键单击该名称并进行命名。
So there's App.css,
just right click on that and say rename.
把一个人放在 css 前面
And just put an s in front of the css.
这不是一个 SASS 课程，我不教你任何 SASS。
So this is not a SASS class,
I'm not teaching you any SASS.
我都不赞成使用 SASS，对吧 ?
I'm not even necessarily
endorsing the use of SASS, right?
我再也不用自己了
I don't use it myself anymore.
但是，所有 css 都是有效的 SASS 或有效的 scss，对，所以
But, all css is valid SASS or
valid scss, right, so
这就是为什么你能改变它而不改变里面的任何东西
that's why you're able to just change it
without changing anything inside of it.
所以我们把它们都命名为 css。
So we name both of these to be s.css.
然后在两个地方你得换个地方
And then in two places
you need to go change.
那么， App.tsx，仅将其更改为 scss。
So, App.tsx, just change that to scss.
他们在 3 号线上然后在 index.tsx上
They're on line 3, and then on index.tsx,
和小童子军一样好吗
same thing here scss, okay?
所以现在我们也有一个 SASSified project ，所以是 TypeScript ，是 SASS
So now we have a SASSified project as
well, so it's TypeScript, it's SASS so
这里有很多依赖关系的人对吧
there's a lot of dependencies
flying around here, right?
所以要确保一切顺利
So just to make sure
that everything works,
我们会说晚上的事开始了我想那是什么
we're gonna say npm run start,
I think is what it is.
我们的计划应以发展模式在本港展开。
And our project should start
locally in the development mode.
我可能还有点东西要从 3000 口开始
I might still have something
running on port 3,000, To start.
好了好了好了
There we go, there you go.
所以，美丽的香草节点项目在这里，对，不是节点，而是 " 雷法" 。
So, pretty vanilla node project here,
right, or not node, but React.
你知道这其实是 React v6 的完整简介
Little did you know this is actually
the complete intro to React v6 and
我们现在就开始了开个玩笑
we're starting now, just kidding.
那将是一个激烈的过程
That would be an intense course,
所有容器都将重新回到容器中。
containers all the way to
React back to containers.
接受挑战
Challenge accepted.
这就是你需要知道的关于这件事的反应。
That's all you need to know about React
for this particular piece of the course.
因此，请继续并停止该服务器。
So go ahead and stop that server.
所以你建造这个项目的方式是你会说 npm 的运行，对吧 ?
So the way that you build this project is
you're gonna say npm run build, right?
这是一个提示它可能要进入你的 Dockerfile，对吧 ?
This is a note to take cuz it's probably
gonna go into your Dockerfile, right?
这会让我们把所有东西都建在
And this'll go through and
this'll actually build everything out into
一个目录，它创造了一个优化的生产结构，对吧 ?
a directory, so it's creating
an optimized production build, right?
因此，这将生成您的所有 index.html，您的 CSS和您的 JavaScript。
So this is gonna generate all of your
index.html, your CSS's, your JavaScripts.
现在，我们有了这个构建目录。
And so now we have this build directory.
所以如果你看看你的建筑目录，你可以看到这里，
So if you look inside of your
build directory, you can see here,
它有一个收藏的，有一个清单，这里有一堆东西，对吧 ?
it's got a favicon, it's got a manifest,
it's got a bunch of stuff in here, right?
那关键是你有一个静态的目录
Then the key here being that
you have a static directory
build/， Static.
build/, Static.
你可以看到有 CSS，有 JS，有媒体，对吧 ?
You can see there's the CSS,
there's JS, there's media, right?
我只想说如果你把整个建筑目录复制
Suffice to say, if you copy
the entire build directory across,
那就是你最后的计划了
that's gonna be your
finally built project.
所以我要你去你的码头
So as such,
I want you to go into your dockerignore,
在你的随机项目中
Inside of your stochastics project.
我们要在这里再加上一条线
And we're gonna add one more line
here to our dockerignore and
就像这样建造的那样
that is going to be, Built, like that.
这样我们就不会像一个预先构建的项目那样意外地复制。
So that we won't accidentally
copy like a pre-built project.
好了这就是我要让你去做这个项目的地方
Okay, so at this point, this is where
I'm gonna leave you to do the project.
你要做的就是多做个多阶段的建筑对吧
So what you're gonna need to do is you're
gonna have a multi-stage build, right?
然后你就会去你的项目
And you're gonna go and
you're going to copy in the project,
你要建这个项目对吧
you're gonna build the project, right?
然后你会把那个输出和
And then,
you're gonna take that output and
你会把它复制到 Nginx 的容器里吧
you're gonna copy it into
a Nginx container, right?
所以我想让你使用的容器
So the container that I want you to use,
如果我们回到这里我的意思是这里有任何东西
if we come back here,
I mean it's anything in here.
你可以做最新的，你可以做高山。
You can do Nginx latest,
you can do alpine.
我想我可以使用 Nginx 117，我认为这是最新的。
I think I have it so you can use Nginx
117, which I believe is the latest.
所以如果你想把它绑在合适的版本上像我说的那样
So if you wanna tie it to a proper version
like I've been telling to do I think
117 是正确的。
117 is the correct one.
让我看看这是否是正确的，我在这里写的。
Let me just triple check that that's the
correct, cuz I have it written out here.
正确版本为 NGINX 1.17。
The correct version is NGINX 1.17.
这就是我想让你在那里使用的
So this is the one that I
want you to use right there.
好吧那就有一个很特别的地方
Okay, and then, so
there's a very specific place that you
要复制它就在这里
have to copy it, Which is here.
因此，将构建文件复制到用户/share/nginx/html，
So copy the build files
to user/share/nginx/html,
所有东西都进了那个目录对吧
everything goes into that directory,
right?
然后不要修改 CMD ，因为 Nginx 知道如何启动它自己。
And then don't modify the CMD, because
Nginx knows how to start itself and so
你不会想改写的
you don't wanna overwrite that.
所以如果你把一切都复制到 Nginx 的正确目录
So if you just copy everything into this
correct directory Nginx will take care of
其余的给你
the rest for you.